guys remember when they said that the aircraft carrier that they have outside of iran was having
plumbing issues so they had to like hold off on operations for a while they had like four hour
uh lines to use the restroom took like 45 minutes to flush the toilet all that
well the plumbers went to go check it out and they came back and they were like yeah the reason why
there's plumbing issues is because there's a bunch of improper materials inside of the pipes
and apparently someone has been flushing a bunch of t-shirts and other things like that into the
pipes so obviously um our own military personnel is sabotaging strikes in iran um the thing that's
so interesting about this you guys is that we are the ones that make all of this shit happen
right we don't realize it we think we have to take orders and shit like that but we're the ones that
make this all happen the only way that a war can happen is if you go out and you decide to comply
with that right and this is what we call well maybe malicious compliance somehow some way right
you guys have to remember the power you have with your labor because they're not going to do it
themselves they're always going to send you in to do their dirty work so don't comply and don't
comply in advance and if you do make sure it's malicious compliance